shalomautohits.com 2008-11-12

# ShalomAutoHits.com: Privacy Policy

What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?

Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, email address) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include receive email newsletters or simply asking a question about ShalomAutoHits.com. ShalomAutoHits.com does not collect personal information from you unless you are a member. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.

Security

Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by ShalomAutoHits.com employees on a _need to know_ basis. All ShalomAutoHits.com employees must go through privacy training upon starting with ShalomAutoHits.com.

email

All email lists maintained by ShalomAutoHits.com contain the names of people who have requested to be a member of ShalomAutoHits.com. The email address collected by ShalomAutoHits.com will never be rented to outside firms for any purposes. 

What anonymous information is collected on this site?

Anonymous information is collected for every visitor to this site. This includes login count, date and time, IP numbers and browser type.

How is it used?

The anonymous information is used by ShalomAutoHits.com to find cheaters.

How does this site use cookies?

ShalomAutoHits.com uses cookies to identify you when you log in. These cookies contain only the entered login information (email address and password).

View for Credits

ShalomAutoHits.com show other Web sites when you view for credits. Please note that when you are viewing for credits, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

Links

ShalomAutoHits.com may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

email Links

We use email links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via email. We use the information provided in your email to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is not shared with third parties.

Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ShalomAutoHits.com.

For more information

If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please email [privacy@ShalomAutoHits.com](mailto:privacy@ShalomAutoHits.com)

Go back
